<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stream</string>
    <string name="playlist">This is the view for the playlists. My favorite UI for a music app is Tidal, and using the BlurredGridMenu would be a neat addition to give it a similiar look</string>
    <string name="tracks">This is the view for individual tracks. Digging around in Android Arsenal I found something called Music Cover View that would provide a cool transition from a list of songs to a song</string>
    <string name="main">Main page of the app for the user to choose what they would like to listen to. One important thing to do would be to add a dialog for permission to use the user\'s location. I found a tool called Simplify Permission from the Android Arsenal that could work with that issue. </string>
    <string name="listen">This layout plays a random song from area. The user has no choice in skipping it (kind of like the radio -but way better music). Also, this gif is supposed to move as the music plays. There is also a Audio Waves tool that moves along with the sound it hears. That could be more therapeutic</string>
    <string name="album">This layout is for the locally available albums in the area</string>>
    <string name="bacon_ipsum">Spicy jalapeno bacon ipsum dolor amet spare ribs enim fugiat shankle jowl picanha. Spare ribs frankfurter laborum bresaola. Voluptate dolore ut meatball beef ribs sint in. Est bresaola beef eu sint. Fatback consectetur hamburger irure. Ipsum esse pancetta adipisicing cillum eu. Ball tip in in, duis rump consectetur qui officia do enim short ribs laboris shankle.\n\nQui veniam sunt, boudin porchetta duis minim excepteur drumstick. Id picanha deserunt ground round turducken excepteur landjaeger culpa pig nulla ut labore in sunt. Est jerky anim, bresaola pork loin ullamco pancetta kielbasa rump. Exercitation shank irure ham. Enim hamburger ipsum, officia nulla anim landjaeger lorem brisket corned beef shankle adipisicing ham. Ham elit turkey nulla swine aute doner. Id aute biltong non, shoulder ut meatball aliqua.\n\nSwine et proident duis shankle sunt bacon pork belly ea dolor nostrud. Incididunt aliquip porchetta leberkas, laboris beef ribs commodo consectetur short ribs kielbasa dolore adipisicing pastrami pig ground round. Short loin est dolore, cupim ut deserunt turducken ribeye bresaola aute bacon pork loin. Deserunt cillum jowl do pork chop velit t-bone hamburger sed pig ea strip steak occaecat veniam eu.\n\nUt ribeye esse jerky cupidatat incididunt turkey fugiat pancetta, pork belly qui adipisicing. Hamburger tempor flank dolor. Kielbasa spare ribs salami pastrami pork loin voluptate nostrud jerky lorem aliquip qui strip steak. Tail strip steak reprehenderit labore eiusmod, pork loin jerky prosciutto et t-bone irure spare ribs brisket capicola laboris. Nostrud occaecat consectetur frankfurter prosciutto pariatur cupidatat jerky sunt.\n\nProsciutto meatball sirloin mollit ullamco labore drumstick sausage cupidatat venison ribeye meatloaf swine. Laboris elit pork loin, pariatur irure ullamco turducken nisi biltong in anim andouille. Chicken est ex esse eiusmod, swine pork adipisicing aute fatback porchetta ut ut pork belly. Et frankfurter pork belly ea ullamco beef. Cupim brisket pariatur tenderloin, kielbasa ex mollit pastrami magna. Occaecat cupidatat laboris sunt andouille ipsum aliqua filet mignon. Bresaola mollit capicola ham hock, velit occaecat id frankfurter.</string>
</resources>
